



phone +31622040319 email info@arejo.nl location The Hague, Netherlands

github github portfolio portfolio linkedin LinkedIn

Startup founder turned developer.

Extremely passionate about building beautiful, practical and smart things. Self-starting, highly determined, obsessively

Having completed the Front-end Engineer Path of the Full-Stack Career Course on codecademy, I am eager to practice my new found skills as a Front-end / React Developer

Open for a junior position or Freelance assignment. Remote / hybrid preferred. Get in touch!

Experience

Dec 2022 - current Arejas The Hague

2021 - 2022 Arejas The Hague

2019/2022 Arejas The Hague

2010-2019 privately held

2016-2017 Camptoo.nl The Hague

2015-2016 Yippie.nl Amsterdam

2011-2014 OWNR The Hague

Freelance Front-end JavaScript Developer

React based web-apps. Current project: Next.js + headless CMS webapp for a local business.

Becoming a Front-end JavaScript Developer

Bootcamp on Codecademy. Completed the Front-End Engineer Path, now continuing for Full-Stack. Studying React / Express. Build and sold a campervan to be able to study fulltime.

Freelance Wordpress Developer

Wordpress websites & webshops for different clients using Divi, Elementor, WooCommerce, HTML and CSS.

miinJohan.nl

Development, Marketing and Sales. Homegrown accountancy software for independent entrepreneurs. Passive Income Company.

Growth Hacker

Head responsible for the growth of the product-offering for this peer-2-peer Campers & Caravans renting platform, using the complete online marketing spectrum including Goal Tracking, Analytics, Split Testing and Conversion Optimisation.

First marketing Officer

Head responsible for the first growth spurt in users of this shopping-app, using the complete online marketing spectrum including Facebook Ads, Google Ads, Goal Tracking, Analytics, Split Testing and Conversion Optimisation.

Startup Founder

Internet startup in action sports. Responsible for marketing, sales, investors, product-development and allround success Collaborations with among others: Quiksilver / DC shoes and Nitro Snowboards.

Building web-apps from start to Rocking React & Redux

HTML JavaScript TypeScript React Redux Node.is Express.js SQL GitHub TDD React Testing Library Markdown Framer Motion

Education

Oct 2022 - Present

2021 - oct 2022

codecademy

2020 - 2021

codecademy

2008-2010

1998-2004

Rotterdam

WdKa

codecademy

Full-Stack Developer Career Path Becoming a Full-Stack web developer learning to build web-apps' front-end and back-end using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Node, Express, SQL, TDD, Mocha, Jest, React

Testing Library, Markdown, JSON, Git & Github.

Frond-End Engineer Career Path

Become a Front-end Engineer. Make UIs and websites beautiful, functional, and fast. Cover all the topics that bootcamps teach (and more). Focus: JavaScript, React, Redux, Data structures, Algorithms, Git & GitHub, TDD

Build a back-end app with JavaScript

A predecessor to codecademy's back-end engineer career path. This was my introduction to JavaScript, Node, Express, SQL and building API's.

Creative Advertising

Art Direction, concepting & realisation. Arts Academy of Rotterdam.

Atheneum

Atheneum. Focus on Economics & Society. Field of choice: Computer Science. Research paper: Encryption.

Google Analytics Goal Tracking **Growth Hacking Principles** Split Testing Conversion Optimalisation Google Adwords Facebook Ads

English German Spanish

Certifications

Ashram College Alphen aan den Rijn

- TypeScript | Learn TypeScript | Codecademy | Oct '22
- Front-End Engineer Career Path | Become a Front-end Engineer | Codecademy | Oct
- Back-end app with Javascript | Write API's with Node, Express & SQL | Codecademy |

Snowboarding Skateboarding Surfing Wakeboarding Climbing Travel Campervans

Adobe Creative Suite Google Sketchup SCRUM